const questions = [
    {
        question: "How did US v Nosal change the interpretation of the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act?",
        options: [
            "US v Nosal changed the CFAA so it’s illegal to share passwords",
            "US v Nosal updated the CFAA so that it prevents former employees from founding new companies to compete with the firms they previously worked for",
            "US v Nosal clarified the CFAA so that it defended against hackers, rather than policing what people post on the Internet and stopping password sharing"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these examples has the strongest case for fair use?",
        options: [
            "Polly made a video singing “All I Want for Christmas is You,” mimicking the costumes and settings from Mariah Carey’s original music video.",
            "Penny made a video critiquing the movie “Elf,” describing various plot holes and making jokes about the incorrect characterization of elves.",
            "Piper printed a copy of the Mona Lisa and made her smile bigger, and then published it on an online art gallery."
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these statements about the Prenda Law case is false?",
        options: [
            "The Prenda Law case took a decade from start to finish.",
            "Prenda Law sued many people for downloading pornography illegally and intimidated them to pay a settlement. If these people didn’t pay a settlement, then it would be revealed publicly that they had illegally downloaded pornography.",
            "The founder of Prenda Law’s conduct was tortious but not illegal."
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a reason why the Library of Congress makes a list of who can engage in circumvention?",
        options: [
            "To protect people from unreasonable searches and seizures",
            "To protect free speech",
            "To protect fair use"
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "In Batzel v. Smith, why was Cremers found not to be liable?",
        options: [
            "Cremers was protected by Section 230 because of his rights to free speech.",
            "Section 230 protected Cremers because he did not have a criminal record.",
            "The court decided that Section 230 protected Cremers because he did not modify Smith’s message."
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following entities would not be allowed to censor free speech?",
        options: [
            "Yale University",
            "Pinterest",
            "University of Vermont"
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following statements are defamatory? Paul told Noelle anonymously that Polly stole a chocolate reindeer and doesn’t know how to read time.",
        options: [
            "Polly is an arrogant jerk.",
            "Polly stole a chocolate reindeer.",
            "Polly doesn't know how to read time."
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following Pamsucks’ posts would give Pim and Pom the best case to disclose their identity?",
        options: [
            "Photo of Pam wrapping a present with caption, \"She hates her job lol\"",
            "Photo of Pam eating a hotdog horizontally with caption, \"HELPPP LOL\"",
            "Photo of Pam talking to another elf with the caption, \"Attention seeker alert!\""
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What’s one reason why Peter Parker’s drone over Pim and Pom’s backyard did not pass the Katz test?",
        options: [
            "It has spider eyes with a camera.",
            "It flies over private property.",
            "The backyard is easily visible to any neighbor."
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How can sharenting make you the product?",
        options: [
            "Sell you dog collars when you don’t have a dog",
            "Give you ads related to your likes, location, and other personal information",
            "Post your digital footprint to your friends on ElfChat"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Why do big companies dislike net neutrality?",
        options: [
            "They don’t want small companies to have handouts",
            "They want to have faster internet lanes by paying more",
            "They believe net neutrality slows down the internet"
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is one benefit of Apple’s strong control over the App Store?",
        options: [
            "It ensures apps are safe and free from malware.",
            "It allows developers to set any price they want.",
            "It gives users complete freedom to customize apps."
        ],
        answer: 0
    },
]
